KADIRI AIYEGBENI ABDULKADIR

69 Iwaya Road, Iwaya, Sabo, Lagos

Email: <u>abdulkadir_kadiri@yahoo.com</u>, <u>kadiriaiyegbenia@gmail.com</u> +234(0)8029693422, +234(0)7054064182

PROFESSIONAL OVERVIEW

A growing professional with over 4years field experience in installation, commissioning, operation and maintenance of electrical, Instrument and telecommunication systems. I am an effective communicator with assertive and strong leadership & analytical qualities that enhances my teamwork and supervision skills. In my quest for professionalism, I look forward to new challenges that will bring out the best in me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EMPLOYER- Bani Networks Global Services

POSITION- Technician

DURATION - JULY, 2019 - TILL DATE

JOB DESCRIPTION

• Preventive maintenance of CCTV surveillance system.

Corrective maintenance of CCTV surveillance system.

Database Management.

PROJECT- SOUTHERN SWAMP ASSOCIATED GAS SOLUTION (SSAGS)
CLIENT- SHELL PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY LIMITED (SPDC)

EMPLOYER- SIELTE NIGERIA LIMITED

POSITION- Technician

DURATION - APRIL, 2017 TO JUNE, 2018

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Interpret and implement electrical, instrument designs and technical drawing.
- Responsible for supervising of assigned electrical and instrument erection works and ensure compliance with quality and safety requirements and supervise the compliance with construction schedule.
- Audit the existing cable plant, junction boxes and supports for compliance to relevant specification and standard.
- Supervised underground and aboveground pulling and connection of cable to the junction boxes and laying of multi core cables through underground route to the technical room.
- Carried out glanding and termination of cables on instrument & telecom equipment and junction boxes, barriers and interface modules.
- Carried out installation, earthing & testing of telecom systems like PAGA, CCTV, ACS, IDS, Telephone, LAN, etc
- Collate man-hours related to proper activity code and forward report to project planner and electrical and instrument superintendent.
- Marking of earth pit around the site.
- Played an active role in the pre-commissioning of instrument & telecom cable plant including loop test, continuity test, leak test and simulation on tubing.
- Participated in site acceptance testing (commissioning) of the installed systems in conjunction with the client.

COMPANY: LED NIGERIA LIMITED
DURATION: JAN 2017 – MAR. 2017
PROJECT: STREETLIGHT AUDITING

POSITION: FIELD Auditor

JOB DESCRIPTION

· Preventive and corrective maintenance planning on street lighting systems in Lagos

- Carried out routine checks on bulkhead, circuit breaker, streetlight, cables, pole cover and poles
- Identify and register GPS location details of poles using SAVEPOINT App.

COMPANY: WARRI REFINING AND PETROCHEMICAL COMPANY LTD

(NNPC)

DURATION: APRIL 2013 –OCTOBER 2013

PROJECT: INDUSTRIAL TRAINING

POSITION: MAINTENANCE ENGINEER (TRAINEE)

JOB DESCRIPTION

- Maintenance of lighting system and switchgears in Power plant areas
- Maintenance of lighting system and current transformer of electrical systems offsite.
- Maintenance and installation of electrical motor.
- Maintenance of pressure transmitters, temperature transmitters, restriction orifice and pressure gauges and valves in the gas and steam turbine process areas.
- Ensure compliance with routine maintenance schedule around the refinery.

EDUCATION

University of Benin, Benin City, Edo State B.Eng Electrical Electronic Engineering	2014
 University Preparatory Secondary School, Benin-City, Edo State Senior School Certificate Examination 	2006
Udo Group of School, Benin-City, Edo State First school leaving Certificate	2000
TRAINING	
Schneider Electric University(electrical Technician lead)	2021
Schneider Electric University(electrical Technician 11)	2020
Schneider Electric University(electrical Technician 1)	2020
Udacity Data Analyst Nanodegree	
Bertelsmann Scholarship	2020
Big Data Analytic	
NIIT	2019
Competency training in Instrumentation and control	
Zery Engineering Nigeria limited	2018
CCTV/Internet Realtime Surveillance Camera Installation and Maintenance	
Medadson Int'l Limited, Port Harcourt	2016

HOBBIES

• Travelling, Reading, football, chess and scrabble.

REFEREES

• Available on request